  
 //{    question: "Answer 5 questions correctly to win. Click here to start the game",
   // answers: {
     // a: "Answer 1",
      //b: "Answer 2",
      //c: "Answer 3",
      //d: "Answer 4"
    //},
    //correctanswer: "0"
  //},
//questions

const myquestions = [
   
    {
      question: "Who is the best teacher in the world?",
      answers: {
        a: "Graydon Scates",
        b: "Princess Taylor",
        c: "Bill Gates",
        d: "Steve Jobs"
      },
      correctanswer: "1"
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the best site ever created?",
      answers: {
        a: "bootcampspot-v2.com",
        b: "Facebook.com",
        c: "Google.com",
        d: "w3schools.com"
      },
      correctanswer: "1"
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the most expensive technology course?",
      answers: {
        a: "Harvard",
        b: "MIT",
        c: "Princeton",
        d: "UCF Bootcamp"
      },
      correctanswer: "4"
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the best city to live?",
      answers: {
        a: "Rio de Janeiro",
        b: "Orlando",
        c: "New York",
        d: "Miami"
      },
      correctanswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the best bootcamp TA?",
      answers: {
        a: "Don Bedwell",
        b: "Stevy Jobson",
        c: "Billy Gateson",
        d: "Larry Ellison"
      },
      correctanswer: "1"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the actual USA's President?",
      answers: {
        a: "Ronald McDonald",
        b: "Barack Obama",
        c: "Donald Trump",
        d: "Donald Duck"
      },
      correctanswer: "3"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the best world's soccer player?",
      answers: {
        a: "Cristov√£o Colombo",
        b: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        c: "Cristian Gray",
        d: "What a Messi"
      },
      correctanswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country wins the 1994's World Cup ?",
      answers: {
        a: "Spain",
        b: "Germany",
        c: "Brazil",
        d: "Argentina"
      },
      correctanswer: "3"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country wins the 1998's World Cup ?",
    answers: {
      a: "France",
      b: "Germany",
      c: "Brazil",
      d: "Argentina"
    },
    correctanswer: "1"
  },
  {
    question: "Which tool uses $() to access methods?",
  answers: {
    a: "Jquery",
    b: "Java Script",
    c: "Bootstrap",
    d: "Html"
  },
  correctanswer: "1"
  },
  
  {
    question: "Which symbol is used to access an array object?",
  answers: {
    a: "Curly Brackets",
    b: "Square Brackets",
    c: "Parenthesis",
    d: "Hashtag"
  },
  correctanswer: "2"
  }
  
  ];
  
  